Follow your dream.
Mrs. Harris Goes to Paris is a drama, comedy,
history film directed by Anthony Fabian.
A 1950s London cleaning lady falls in love with an haute couture dress by Christian
Dior and decides to gamble everything for the sake of this folly.
Ada Harris, played by Lesley Manville.
Claudine Colbert, played by Isabelle Huppert.
Marquis de Chassagne, played by Lambert Wilson.
Natasha, played by Alba Baptista.
André Fauvel, played by Lucas Bravo.
Vi Butterfield, played by Ellen Thomas.
Harris Goes to Paris is a 2022 historical comedy drama film directed and produced by Anthony Fabian,
from a screenplay he co-wrote with Carroll Cartwright, Keith Thompson, and Olivia Hetreed.
It is the third film adaptation of the 1958 novel Mrs.
'Arris Goes to Paris by Paul Gallico.
The film stars Lesley Manville, Isabelle Huppert, Lambert Wilson, Alba
Baptista, Lucas Bravo, Ellen Thomas, Rose Williams, and Jason Isaacs.
The film enjoyed strong box office success in the
United States arthouse circuit.
Manville received a nomination for the Golden Globe Award for Best Actress
in a Motion Picture – Comedy or Musical for her performance.
The film also won a British Independent Film Award and received a nomination
for an Academy Award and a BAFTA Award for Best Costume Design.
The film explores themes of paris, france, based on
novel or book, widow, dress, fashion.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.